{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_65","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671389640","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671389640"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" null"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" null"," tutorId":" null"," matrixName":" null"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" null"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" null"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671389702","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671389702"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 3cbd2a27-cbbb-4170-8c37-cd001f432e27"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale wasichana watatu walienda kutafuta kuni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATATU"," userResponse":" WATATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_66","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671397944","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671397944"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 3cbd2a27-cbbb-4170-8c37-cd001f432e27"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale wasichana watatu walienda kutafuta kuni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671406711","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671406711"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 3cbd2a27-cbbb-4170-8c37-cd001f432e27"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale wasichana watatu walienda kutafuta kuni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_41","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671415854","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671415854"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 3cbd2a27-cbbb-4170-8c37-cd001f432e27"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.clo.hear__story_65"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale wasichana watatu walienda kutafuta kuni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671432018","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671432018"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 8f4e2211-dbd0-40ef-81f2-290a17d4b7c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_8_8-9-11"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 8"," userResponse":" 8"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671437779","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671437779"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 8f4e2211-dbd0-40ef-81f2-290a17d4b7c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_4_1-2-4"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671442402","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671442401"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 8f4e2211-dbd0-40ef-81f2-290a17d4b7c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_0_0-1-5"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671448146","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671448146"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 8f4e2211-dbd0-40ef-81f2-290a17d4b7c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_1-10-6"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671453873","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671453873"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 8f4e2211-dbd0-40ef-81f2-290a17d4b7c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_3-5-7"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671462306","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671462306"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 8f4e2211-dbd0-40ef-81f2-290a17d4b7c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_1_8-1-10"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671472426","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671472426"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 8f4e2211-dbd0-40ef-81f2-290a17d4b7c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_8-3-4"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671480073","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671480073"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 8f4e2211-dbd0-40ef-81f2-290a17d4b7c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_9_0-9-13"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671486992","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671486992"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 8f4e2211-dbd0-40ef-81f2-290a17d4b7c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_7_0-10-7"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 7"," userResponse":" 7"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671493749","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671493749"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 8f4e2211-dbd0-40ef-81f2-290a17d4b7c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_0_0-12-6"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671500478","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671500477"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 8f4e2211-dbd0-40ef-81f2-290a17d4b7c2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF1-BL1.incr.4"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_0_0-12-6"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:R..R.all.rand.all.stat.show.110","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671511566","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671511565"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" b0fe736b-bba1-4a53-9d38-3b263ff17280"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_R..R.all.rand.all.stat.show.110"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_r_w-a-r"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" r"," userResponse":" r"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:R..R.all.rand.all.stat.show.110","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671516231","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671516230"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" b0fe736b-bba1-4a53-9d38-3b263ff17280"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_R..R.all.rand.all.stat.show.110"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_r_r-n-v"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" r"," userResponse":" r"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:R..R.all.rand.all.stat.show.110","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671520476","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671520476"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" b0fe736b-bba1-4a53-9d38-3b263ff17280"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_R..R.all.rand.all.stat.show.110"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_r_y-r-p"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" r"," userResponse":" r"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:R..R.all.rand.all.stat.show.110","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671524117","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671524117"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" b0fe736b-bba1-4a53-9d38-3b263ff17280"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_R..R.all.rand.all.stat.show.110"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_r_i-r-v"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" r"," userResponse":" r"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:R..R.all.rand.all.stat.show.110","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671527631","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671527630"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" b0fe736b-bba1-4a53-9d38-3b263ff17280"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_R..R.all.rand.all.stat.show.110"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_r_y-r-o"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" r"," userResponse":" r"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:R..R.all.rand.all.stat.show.110","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671531418","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671531418"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" b0fe736b-bba1-4a53-9d38-3b263ff17280"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_R..R.all.rand.all.stat.show.110"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_r_j-b-r"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" r"," userResponse":" r"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:R..R.all.rand.all.stat.show.110","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671535137","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671535137"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" b0fe736b-bba1-4a53-9d38-3b263ff17280"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_R..R.all.rand.all.stat.show.110"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_r_o-p-r"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" r"," userResponse":" r"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:R..R.all.rand.all.stat.show.110","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671538915","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671538915"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" b0fe736b-bba1-4a53-9d38-3b263ff17280"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_R..R.all.rand.all.stat.show.110"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_r_r-j-u"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" r"," userResponse":" j"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:R..R.all.rand.all.stat.show.110","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671544117","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671544117"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" b0fe736b-bba1-4a53-9d38-3b263ff17280"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_R..R.all.rand.all.stat.show.110"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_r_r-j-u"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" r"," userResponse":" r"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:R..R.all.rand.all.stat.show.110","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671548093","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671548093"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" b0fe736b-bba1-4a53-9d38-3b263ff17280"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_R..R.all.rand.all.stat.show.110"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_r_r-o-f"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" r"," userResponse":" r"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:R..R.all.rand.all.stat.show.110","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671552119","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671552119"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" b0fe736b-bba1-4a53-9d38-3b263ff17280"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_R..R.all.rand.all.stat.show.110"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_r_ch-j-r"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" r"," userResponse":" r"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:R..R.all.rand.all.stat.show.110","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671557841","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671557841"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" b0fe736b-bba1-4a53-9d38-3b263ff17280"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_R..R.all.rand.all.stat.show.110"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_r_ch-j-r"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671568398","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671568398"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi na kunguru walikuwa marafiki sana hapo awali ingawaje tabia zao zilikuwa tofauti sana kwa njia nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FISI"," userResponse":" FISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671568596","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671568595"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi na kunguru walikuwa marafiki sana hapo awali ingawaje tabia zao zilikuwa tofauti sana kwa njia nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671569400","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671569400"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi na kunguru walikuwa marafiki sana hapo awali ingawaje tabia zao zilikuwa tofauti sana kwa njia nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" KUNGURU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671570056","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671570055"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi na kunguru walikuwa marafiki sana hapo awali ingawaje tabia zao zilikuwa tofauti sana kwa njia nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIKUWA"," userResponse":" WALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671570830","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671570830"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi na kunguru walikuwa marafiki sana hapo awali ingawaje tabia zao zilikuwa tofauti sana kwa njia nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MARAFIKI"," userResponse":" MARAFIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671571384","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671571384"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi na kunguru walikuwa marafiki sana hapo awali ingawaje tabia zao zilikuwa tofauti sana kwa njia nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671572328","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671572328"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi na kunguru walikuwa marafiki sana hapo awali ingawaje tabia zao zilikuwa tofauti sana kwa njia nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPO"," userResponse":" HAPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671573052","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671573051"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi na kunguru walikuwa marafiki sana hapo awali ingawaje tabia zao zilikuwa tofauti sana kwa njia nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AWALI"," userResponse":" AWALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671574196","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671574195"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi na kunguru walikuwa marafiki sana hapo awali ingawaje tabia zao zilikuwa tofauti sana kwa njia nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" INGAWAJE"," userResponse":" INGAWAJE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671574770","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671574770"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi na kunguru walikuwa marafiki sana hapo awali ingawaje tabia zao zilikuwa tofauti sana kwa njia nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TABIA"," userResponse":" TABIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671575355","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671575355"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi na kunguru walikuwa marafiki sana hapo awali ingawaje tabia zao zilikuwa tofauti sana kwa njia nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAO"," userResponse":" ZAO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671576450","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671576450"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi na kunguru walikuwa marafiki sana hapo awali ingawaje tabia zao zilikuwa tofauti sana kwa njia nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZILIKUWA"," userResponse":" ZILIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671577323","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671577322"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi na kunguru walikuwa marafiki sana hapo awali ingawaje tabia zao zilikuwa tofauti sana kwa njia nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TOFAUTI"," userResponse":" TOFAUTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671578238","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671578238"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi na kunguru walikuwa marafiki sana hapo awali ingawaje tabia zao zilikuwa tofauti sana kwa njia nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671578984","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671578984"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi na kunguru walikuwa marafiki sana hapo awali ingawaje tabia zao zilikuwa tofauti sana kwa njia nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671579434","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671579433"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi na kunguru walikuwa marafiki sana hapo awali ingawaje tabia zao zilikuwa tofauti sana kwa njia nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 15"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJIA"," userResponse":" NJIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671580199","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671580198"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi na kunguru walikuwa marafiki sana hapo awali ingawaje tabia zao zilikuwa tofauti sana kwa njia nyingine."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 16"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYINGINE"," userResponse":" NYINGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671582845","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671582845"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru aliweza kuruka lakini fisi hakuweza isipokuwa kutembea tu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" KUNGURU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671583560","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671583560"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru aliweza kuruka lakini fisi hakuweza isipokuwa kutembea tu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIWEZA"," userResponse":" ALIWEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671584294","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671584294"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru aliweza kuruka lakini fisi hakuweza isipokuwa kutembea tu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KURUKA"," userResponse":" KURUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671585267","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671585267"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru aliweza kuruka lakini fisi hakuweza isipokuwa kutembea tu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671585721","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671585720"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru aliweza kuruka lakini fisi hakuweza isipokuwa kutembea tu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FISI"," userResponse":" FISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671586623","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671586623"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru aliweza kuruka lakini fisi hakuweza isipokuwa kutembea tu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAKUWEZA"," userResponse":" HAKUWEZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671587777","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671587776"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru aliweza kuruka lakini fisi hakuweza isipokuwa kutembea tu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ISIPOKUWA"," userResponse":" ISIPOKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671588590","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671588590"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru aliweza kuruka lakini fisi hakuweza isipokuwa kutembea tu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTEMBEA"," userResponse":" KUTEMBEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671588923","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671588923"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru aliweza kuruka lakini fisi hakuweza isipokuwa kutembea tu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TU"," userResponse":" TU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671591875","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671591875"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwuliza kunguru kitu hiki cheupe kilichopo nyuma ya shingo lako ni kitu gani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKU"," userResponse":" SIKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671592488","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671592488"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwuliza kunguru kitu hiki cheupe kilichopo nyuma ya shingo lako ni kitu gani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MOJA"," userResponse":" MOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671593302","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671593302"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwuliza kunguru kitu hiki cheupe kilichopo nyuma ya shingo lako ni kitu gani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FISI"," userResponse":" FISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671593885","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671593885"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwuliza kunguru kitu hiki cheupe kilichopo nyuma ya shingo lako ni kitu gani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671594068","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671594068"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwuliza kunguru kitu hiki cheupe kilichopo nyuma ya shingo lako ni kitu gani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671594682","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671594681"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwuliza kunguru kitu hiki cheupe kilichopo nyuma ya shingo lako ni kitu gani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAMU"," userResponse":" HAMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671596295","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671596295"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwuliza kunguru kitu hiki cheupe kilichopo nyuma ya shingo lako ni kitu gani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMFAHAMU"," userResponse":" KUMFAHAMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671597258","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671597258"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwuliza kunguru kitu hiki cheupe kilichopo nyuma ya shingo lako ni kitu gani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAIDI"," userResponse":" ZAIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671597830","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671597829"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwuliza kunguru kitu hiki cheupe kilichopo nyuma ya shingo lako ni kitu gani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAFIKI"," userResponse":" RAFIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671598266","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671598265"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwuliza kunguru kitu hiki cheupe kilichopo nyuma ya shingo lako ni kitu gani?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671601093","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671601093"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwuliza kunguru kitu hiki cheupe kilichopo nyuma ya shingo lako ni kitu gani?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMWULIZA"," userResponse":" ALIMWULIZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671601727","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671601727"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwuliza kunguru kitu hiki cheupe kilichopo nyuma ya shingo lako ni kitu gani?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" KUNGURU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671602803","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671602802"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwuliza kunguru kitu hiki cheupe kilichopo nyuma ya shingo lako ni kitu gani?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITU"," userResponse":" KITU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671603257","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671603257"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwuliza kunguru kitu hiki cheupe kilichopo nyuma ya shingo lako ni kitu gani?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIKI"," userResponse":" HIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671604051","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671604050"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwuliza kunguru kitu hiki cheupe kilichopo nyuma ya shingo lako ni kitu gani?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHEUPE"," userResponse":" CHEUPE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671604905","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671604905"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwuliza kunguru kitu hiki cheupe kilichopo nyuma ya shingo lako ni kitu gani?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KILICHOPO"," userResponse":" KILICHOPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671605279","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671605279"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwuliza kunguru kitu hiki cheupe kilichopo nyuma ya shingo lako ni kitu gani?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYUMA"," userResponse":" NYUMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671605382","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671605382"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwuliza kunguru kitu hiki cheupe kilichopo nyuma ya shingo lako ni kitu gani?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671605757","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671605757"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwuliza kunguru kitu hiki cheupe kilichopo nyuma ya shingo lako ni kitu gani?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHINGO"," userResponse":" SHINGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671606440","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671606439"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwuliza kunguru kitu hiki cheupe kilichopo nyuma ya shingo lako ni kitu gani?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKO"," userResponse":" LAKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671606941","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671606941"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwuliza kunguru kitu hiki cheupe kilichopo nyuma ya shingo lako ni kitu gani?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671607299","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671607299"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwuliza kunguru kitu hiki cheupe kilichopo nyuma ya shingo lako ni kitu gani?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KITU"," userResponse":" KITU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671608165","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671608165"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwuliza kunguru kitu hiki cheupe kilichopo nyuma ya shingo lako ni kitu gani?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GANI"," userResponse":" GANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671610020","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671610020"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimekuwa ninaila tangu muda mrefu hadi sasa imenibandika shingoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NI"," userResponse":" NI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671610610","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671610608"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimekuwa ninaila tangu muda mrefu hadi sasa imenibandika shingoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYAMA"," userResponse":" NYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671611532","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671611532"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimekuwa ninaila tangu muda mrefu hadi sasa imenibandika shingoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NONO"," userResponse":" NONO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671612386","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671612385"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimekuwa ninaila tangu muda mrefu hadi sasa imenibandika shingoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMBAYO"," userResponse":" AMBAYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671613146","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671613146"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimekuwa ninaila tangu muda mrefu hadi sasa imenibandika shingoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAWAIDA"," userResponse":" KAWAIDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671614040","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671614040"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimekuwa ninaila tangu muda mrefu hadi sasa imenibandika shingoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" INALIWA"," userResponse":" INALIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671615074","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671615074"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimekuwa ninaila tangu muda mrefu hadi sasa imenibandika shingoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKATI"," userResponse":" WAKATI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671616014","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671616013"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimekuwa ninaila tangu muda mrefu hadi sasa imenibandika shingoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINAPORUKA"," userResponse":" NINAPORUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671616713","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671616713"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimekuwa ninaila tangu muda mrefu hadi sasa imenibandika shingoni."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGANI"," userResponse":" ANGANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671619380","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671619379"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimekuwa ninaila tangu muda mrefu hadi sasa imenibandika shingoni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIMEKUWA"," userResponse":" NIMEKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671620423","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671620423"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimekuwa ninaila tangu muda mrefu hadi sasa imenibandika shingoni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINAILA"," userResponse":" NINAILA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671621417","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671621417"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimekuwa ninaila tangu muda mrefu hadi sasa imenibandika shingoni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANGU"," userResponse":" TANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671621786","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671621785"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimekuwa ninaila tangu muda mrefu hadi sasa imenibandika shingoni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUDA"," userResponse":" MUDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671622507","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671622507"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimekuwa ninaila tangu muda mrefu hadi sasa imenibandika shingoni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MREFU"," userResponse":" MREFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671623548","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671623547"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimekuwa ninaila tangu muda mrefu hadi sasa imenibandika shingoni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HADI"," userResponse":" HADI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671624117","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671624116"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimekuwa ninaila tangu muda mrefu hadi sasa imenibandika shingoni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SASA"," userResponse":" SASA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671625595","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671625594"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimekuwa ninaila tangu muda mrefu hadi sasa imenibandika shingoni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IMENIBANDIKA"," userResponse":" IMENIBANDIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671626478","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671626477"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nimekuwa ninaila tangu muda mrefu hadi sasa imenibandika shingoni."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHINGONI"," userResponse":" SHINGONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671630204","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671630204"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliposikia juu ya nyama fisi alitokwa na udenda katika tamaa yake ya kula nyama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOSIKIA"," userResponse":" ALIPOSIKIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671630684","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671630684"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliposikia juu ya nyama fisi alitokwa na udenda katika tamaa yake ya kula nyama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUU"," userResponse":" JUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671630815","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671630814"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliposikia juu ya nyama fisi alitokwa na udenda katika tamaa yake ya kula nyama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671631479","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671631478"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliposikia juu ya nyama fisi alitokwa na udenda katika tamaa yake ya kula nyama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYAMA"," userResponse":" NYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671632524","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671632524"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliposikia juu ya nyama fisi alitokwa na udenda katika tamaa yake ya kula nyama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FISI"," userResponse":" FISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671633494","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671633493"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliposikia juu ya nyama fisi alitokwa na udenda katika tamaa yake ya kula nyama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALITOKWA"," userResponse":" ALITOKWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671633732","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671633732"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliposikia juu ya nyama fisi alitokwa na udenda katika tamaa yake ya kula nyama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671634404","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671634404"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliposikia juu ya nyama fisi alitokwa na udenda katika tamaa yake ya kula nyama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UDENDA"," userResponse":" UDENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671635298","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671635298"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliposikia juu ya nyama fisi alitokwa na udenda katika tamaa yake ya kula nyama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" KATIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671635863","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671635862"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliposikia juu ya nyama fisi alitokwa na udenda katika tamaa yake ya kula nyama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAMAA"," userResponse":" TAMAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671636402","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671636401"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliposikia juu ya nyama fisi alitokwa na udenda katika tamaa yake ya kula nyama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671636510","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671636510"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliposikia juu ya nyama fisi alitokwa na udenda katika tamaa yake ya kula nyama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671636883","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671636882"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliposikia juu ya nyama fisi alitokwa na udenda katika tamaa yake ya kula nyama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULA"," userResponse":" KULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671637361","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671637361"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aliposikia juu ya nyama fisi alitokwa na udenda katika tamaa yake ya kula nyama."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYAMA"," userResponse":" NYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671639694","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671639693"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini ataipataje ikiwa juu angani hali hana mbawa ya kuirukia?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FISI"," userResponse":" FISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671640644","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671640643"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini ataipataje ikiwa juu angani hali hana mbawa ya kuirukia?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALITAMANI"," userResponse":" ALITAMANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671641382","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671641381"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini ataipataje ikiwa juu angani hali hana mbawa ya kuirukia?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671642123","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671642122"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini ataipataje ikiwa juu angani hali hana mbawa ya kuirukia?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULA"," userResponse":" KULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671642660","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671642659"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini ataipataje ikiwa juu angani hali hana mbawa ya kuirukia?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYAMA"," userResponse":" NYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671643186","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671643185"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini ataipataje ikiwa juu angani hali hana mbawa ya kuirukia?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIYO"," userResponse":" HIYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671646004","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671646003"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini ataipataje ikiwa juu angani hali hana mbawa ya kuirukia?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671647690","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671647689"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini ataipataje ikiwa juu angani hali hana mbawa ya kuirukia?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ATAIPATAJE"," userResponse":" ATAIPATAJE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671648413","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671648413"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini ataipataje ikiwa juu angani hali hana mbawa ya kuirukia?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IKIWA"," userResponse":" IKIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671648850","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671648850"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini ataipataje ikiwa juu angani hali hana mbawa ya kuirukia?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUU"," userResponse":" JUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671649731","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671649730"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini ataipataje ikiwa juu angani hali hana mbawa ya kuirukia?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGANI"," userResponse":" ANGANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671650259","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671650259"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini ataipataje ikiwa juu angani hali hana mbawa ya kuirukia?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HALI"," userResponse":" HALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671650806","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671650805"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini ataipataje ikiwa juu angani hali hana mbawa ya kuirukia?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HANA"," userResponse":" HANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671651334","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671651334"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini ataipataje ikiwa juu angani hali hana mbawa ya kuirukia?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBAWA"," userResponse":" MBAWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671651533","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671651532"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini ataipataje ikiwa juu angani hali hana mbawa ya kuirukia?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671652624","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671652624"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini ataipataje ikiwa juu angani hali hana mbawa ya kuirukia?"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUIRUKIA"," userResponse":" KUIRUKIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671655252","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671655252"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAFADHALI"," userResponse":" TAFADHALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671655947","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671655947"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAFIKI"," userResponse":" RAFIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671656630","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671656629"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" YANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671657570","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671657570"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAOMBA"," userResponse":" NAOMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671658461","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671658460"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUKOPESHA"," userResponse":" KUKOPESHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671659266","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671659266"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYOYA"," userResponse":" MANYOYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671660003","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671660003"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILI"," userResponse":" ILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671660599","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671660599"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIWEZE"," userResponse":" NIWEZE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671661943","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671661943"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUJITENGENEZEA"," userResponse":" KUJITENGENEZEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671662692","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671662691"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBAWA"," userResponse":" MBAWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671665185","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671665185"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINA"," userResponse":" NINA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671665658","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671665658"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAMU"," userResponse":" HAMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671666596","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671666596"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671667481","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671667480"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KURUKA"," userResponse":" KURUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671668046","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671668046"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMA"," userResponse":" KAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671668596","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671668596"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WEWE"," userResponse":" WEWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671671390","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671671389"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMWOMBA"," userResponse":" ALIMWOMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671672115","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671672114"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" KUNGURU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671675246","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671675245"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru kwa ukarimu wake alimpa fisi manyoya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" KUNGURU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671675435","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671675435"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru kwa ukarimu wake alimpa fisi manyoya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671676211","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671676211"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru kwa ukarimu wake alimpa fisi manyoya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UKARIMU"," userResponse":" UKARIMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671676650","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671676649"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru kwa ukarimu wake alimpa fisi manyoya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671677730","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671677730"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru kwa ukarimu wake alimpa fisi manyoya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMPA"," userResponse":" ALIMPA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671678218","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671678218"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru kwa ukarimu wake alimpa fisi manyoya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FISI"," userResponse":" FISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671678939","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671678938"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru kwa ukarimu wake alimpa fisi manyoya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYOYA"," userResponse":" MANYOYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671681284","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671681284"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi aliyashona yawe mbawa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FISI"," userResponse":" FISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671682517","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671682517"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi aliyashona yawe mbawa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYASHONA"," userResponse":" ALIYASHONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671683007","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671683007"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi aliyashona yawe mbawa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAWE"," userResponse":" YAWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671683620","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671683619"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi aliyashona yawe mbawa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBAWA"," userResponse":" MBAWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671686958","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671686958"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akayaunganisha na mwili wake akajaribu kuruka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAYAUNGANISHA"," userResponse":" AKAYAUNGANISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671687234","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671687233"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akayaunganisha na mwili wake akajaribu kuruka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671687744","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671687744"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akayaunganisha na mwili wake akajaribu kuruka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWILI"," userResponse":" MWILI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671688308","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671688308"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akayaunganisha na mwili wake akajaribu kuruka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671689612","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671689612"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akayaunganisha na mwili wake akajaribu kuruka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAJARIBU"," userResponse":" AKAJARIBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671690298","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671690298"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Akayaunganisha na mwili wake akajaribu kuruka."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KURUKA"," userResponse":" KURUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671693115","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671693115"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini uzito wake ulimshinda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671693653","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671693653"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini uzito wake ulimshinda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UZITO"," userResponse":" UZITO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671694034","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671694033"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini uzito wake ulimshinda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671694961","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671694961"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini uzito wake ulimshinda."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIMSHINDA"," userResponse":" ULIMSHINDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671697705","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671697704"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa ilibidi afikirie mpango mpya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SASA"," userResponse":" SASA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671698617","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671698617"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa ilibidi afikirie mpango mpya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIBIDI"," userResponse":" ILIBIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671699484","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671699484"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa ilibidi afikirie mpango mpya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AFIKIRIE"," userResponse":" AFIKIRIE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671700065","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671700065"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa ilibidi afikirie mpango mpya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MPANGO"," userResponse":" MPANGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671700679","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671700678"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sasa ilibidi afikirie mpango mpya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MPYA"," userResponse":" MPYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671704575","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671704574"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAFADHALI"," userResponse":" TAFADHALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671705291","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671705291"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAFIKI"," userResponse":" RAFIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671705706","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671705705"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" YANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671706765","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671706765"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAOMBA"," userResponse":" NAOMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671707846","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671707845"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NIKUSHIKE"," userResponse":" NIKUSHIKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671707997","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671707997"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671708623","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671708623"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKIA"," userResponse":" MKIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671709256","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671709255"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKO"," userResponse":" WAKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671710651","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671710651"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UTAKAPORUKA"," userResponse":" UTAKAPORUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671711597","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671711596"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGANI"," userResponse":" ANGANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671714445","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671714444"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMWOMBA"," userResponse":" ALIMWOMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671715169","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671715169"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alimwomba kunguru."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" KUNGURU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671717668","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671717667"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hebu tufanye kesho asubuhi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAWA"," userResponse":" SAWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671718224","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671718223"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hebu tufanye kesho asubuhi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAWA"," userResponse":" SAWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671719381","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671719380"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hebu tufanye kesho asubuhi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAKUBALI"," userResponse":" AKAKUBALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671720004","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671720004"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hebu tufanye kesho asubuhi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" KUNGURU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671722990","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671722990"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hebu tufanye kesho asubuhi."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAJUA"," userResponse":" NAJUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671723366","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671723366"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hebu tufanye kesho asubuhi."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UNA"," userResponse":" UNA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671723840","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671723840"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hebu tufanye kesho asubuhi."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAMU"," userResponse":" HAMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671724513","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671724513"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hebu tufanye kesho asubuhi."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KURUKA"," userResponse":" KURUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671727148","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671727148"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hebu tufanye kesho asubuhi."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HEBU"," userResponse":" HEBU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671727774","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671727774"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hebu tufanye kesho asubuhi."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUFANYE"," userResponse":" TUFANYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671728220","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671728219"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hebu tufanye kesho asubuhi."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KESHO"," userResponse":" KESHO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671729086","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671729086"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hebu tufanye kesho asubuhi."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ASUBUHI"," userResponse":" ASUBUHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671732567","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671732566"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilipokucha kesho yake fisi alimshika kunguru kwa mkia wake naye kunguru akaruka angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIPOKUCHA"," userResponse":" ILIPOKUCHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671733010","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671733009"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilipokucha kesho yake fisi alimshika kunguru kwa mkia wake naye kunguru akaruka angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KESHO"," userResponse":" KESHO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671733692","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671733692"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilipokucha kesho yake fisi alimshika kunguru kwa mkia wake naye kunguru akaruka angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671734711","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671734711"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilipokucha kesho yake fisi alimshika kunguru kwa mkia wake naye kunguru akaruka angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FISI"," userResponse":" FISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671735638","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671735637"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilipokucha kesho yake fisi alimshika kunguru kwa mkia wake naye kunguru akaruka angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIMSHIKA"," userResponse":" ALIMSHIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671736034","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671736034"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilipokucha kesho yake fisi alimshika kunguru kwa mkia wake naye kunguru akaruka angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" KUNGURU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671736636","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671736636"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilipokucha kesho yake fisi alimshika kunguru kwa mkia wake naye kunguru akaruka angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671737143","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671737142"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilipokucha kesho yake fisi alimshika kunguru kwa mkia wake naye kunguru akaruka angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKIA"," userResponse":" MKIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671737676","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671737675"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilipokucha kesho yake fisi alimshika kunguru kwa mkia wake naye kunguru akaruka angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671738507","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671738506"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilipokucha kesho yake fisi alimshika kunguru kwa mkia wake naye kunguru akaruka angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NAYE"," userResponse":" NAYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671739183","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671739182"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilipokucha kesho yake fisi alimshika kunguru kwa mkia wake naye kunguru akaruka angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" KUNGURU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671739917","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671739917"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilipokucha kesho yake fisi alimshika kunguru kwa mkia wake naye kunguru akaruka angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKARUKA"," userResponse":" AKARUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671740721","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671740721"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ilipokucha kesho yake fisi alimshika kunguru kwa mkia wake naye kunguru akaruka angani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGANI"," userResponse":" ANGANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671743551","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671743550"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi alikuwa akitamani nyama iliyokuwa juu mbele kidogo akatokwa na udenda tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FISI"," userResponse":" FISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671744346","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671744346"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi alikuwa akitamani nyama iliyokuwa juu mbele kidogo akatokwa na udenda tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671745452","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671745451"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi alikuwa akitamani nyama iliyokuwa juu mbele kidogo akatokwa na udenda tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKITAMANI"," userResponse":" AKITAMANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671746054","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671746053"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi alikuwa akitamani nyama iliyokuwa juu mbele kidogo akatokwa na udenda tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYAMA"," userResponse":" NYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671746945","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671746944"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi alikuwa akitamani nyama iliyokuwa juu mbele kidogo akatokwa na udenda tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ILIYOKUWA"," userResponse":" ILIYOKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671747869","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671747868"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi alikuwa akitamani nyama iliyokuwa juu mbele kidogo akatokwa na udenda tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUU"," userResponse":" JUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671748778","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671748778"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi alikuwa akitamani nyama iliyokuwa juu mbele kidogo akatokwa na udenda tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBELE"," userResponse":" MBELE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671749532","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671749531"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi alikuwa akitamani nyama iliyokuwa juu mbele kidogo akatokwa na udenda tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIDOGO"," userResponse":" KIDOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671750435","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671750434"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi alikuwa akitamani nyama iliyokuwa juu mbele kidogo akatokwa na udenda tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKATOKWA"," userResponse":" AKATOKWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671750592","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671750592"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi alikuwa akitamani nyama iliyokuwa juu mbele kidogo akatokwa na udenda tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671751290","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671751290"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi alikuwa akitamani nyama iliyokuwa juu mbele kidogo akatokwa na udenda tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UDENDA"," userResponse":" UDENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671751787","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671751786"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fisi alikuwa akitamani nyama iliyokuwa juu mbele kidogo akatokwa na udenda tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 11"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TENA"," userResponse":" TENA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671754252","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671754251"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini fisi akamwomba endelea kidogo tu rafiki yangu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" KUNGURU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671755517","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671755516"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini fisi akamwomba endelea kidogo tu rafiki yangu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIRUKA"," userResponse":" ALIRUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671756148","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671756147"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini fisi akamwomba endelea kidogo tu rafiki yangu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671757179","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671757178"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini fisi akamwomba endelea kidogo tu rafiki yangu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KURUKA"," userResponse":" KURUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671758252","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671758251"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini fisi akamwomba endelea kidogo tu rafiki yangu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MPAKA"," userResponse":" MPAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671759420","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671759419"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini fisi akamwomba endelea kidogo tu rafiki yangu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKACHOKA"," userResponse":" AKACHOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671760068","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671760067"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini fisi akamwomba endelea kidogo tu rafiki yangu!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KABISA"," userResponse":" KABISA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671762774","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671762773"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini fisi akamwomba endelea kidogo tu rafiki yangu!"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671763287","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671763286"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini fisi akamwomba endelea kidogo tu rafiki yangu!"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FISI"," userResponse":" FISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671764275","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671764275"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini fisi akamwomba endelea kidogo tu rafiki yangu!"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAMWOMBA"," userResponse":" AKAMWOMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671765688","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671765688"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini fisi akamwomba endelea kidogo tu rafiki yangu!"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ENDELEA"," userResponse":" ENDELEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671766447","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671766446"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini fisi akamwomba endelea kidogo tu rafiki yangu!"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIDOGO"," userResponse":" KIDOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671766783","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671766783"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini fisi akamwomba endelea kidogo tu rafiki yangu!"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TU"," userResponse":" TU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671767554","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671767553"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini fisi akamwomba endelea kidogo tu rafiki yangu!"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAFIKI"," userResponse":" RAFIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671767940","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671767939"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini fisi akamwomba endelea kidogo tu rafiki yangu!"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YANGU"," userResponse":" YANGU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671771616","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671771615"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipofika kipande cha kwanza cha nyama nono fisi alisikia mshtuko."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIPOFIKA"," userResponse":" WALIPOFIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671772437","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671772437"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipofika kipande cha kwanza cha nyama nono fisi alisikia mshtuko."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIPANDE"," userResponse":" KIPANDE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671772764","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671772764"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipofika kipande cha kwanza cha nyama nono fisi alisikia mshtuko."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" CHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671773440","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671773440"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipofika kipande cha kwanza cha nyama nono fisi alisikia mshtuko."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671773980","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671773980"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipofika kipande cha kwanza cha nyama nono fisi alisikia mshtuko."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHA"," userResponse":" CHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671774467","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671774467"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipofika kipande cha kwanza cha nyama nono fisi alisikia mshtuko."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYAMA"," userResponse":" NYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671775136","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671775136"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipofika kipande cha kwanza cha nyama nono fisi alisikia mshtuko."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NONO"," userResponse":" NONO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671776019","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671776018"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipofika kipande cha kwanza cha nyama nono fisi alisikia mshtuko."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FISI"," userResponse":" FISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671776995","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671776994"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipofika kipande cha kwanza cha nyama nono fisi alisikia mshtuko."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISIKIA"," userResponse":" ALISIKIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671778217","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671778216"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Walipofika kipande cha kwanza cha nyama nono fisi alisikia mshtuko."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSHTUKO"," userResponse":" MSHTUKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671780814","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671780813"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru alijisikia ameondolewa na mzigo na mkia wake ukapona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UNYOYA"," userResponse":" UNYOYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671781567","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671781567"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru alijisikia ameondolewa na mzigo na mkia wake ukapona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671782896","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671782895"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru alijisikia ameondolewa na mzigo na mkia wake ukapona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIOUSHIKA"," userResponse":" ALIOUSHIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671784076","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671784075"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru alijisikia ameondolewa na mzigo na mkia wake ukapona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UKATOKA"," userResponse":" UKATOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671784728","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671784727"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru alijisikia ameondolewa na mzigo na mkia wake ukapona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKIA"," userResponse":" MKIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671784979","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671784979"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru alijisikia ameondolewa na mzigo na mkia wake ukapona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671785714","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671785713"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru alijisikia ameondolewa na mzigo na mkia wake ukapona."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" KUNGURU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671787964","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671787963"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru alijisikia ameondolewa na mzigo na mkia wake ukapona."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KISHA"," userResponse":" KISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671788865","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671788865"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru alijisikia ameondolewa na mzigo na mkia wake ukapona."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSHTUKO"," userResponse":" MSHTUKO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671789523","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671789523"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru alijisikia ameondolewa na mzigo na mkia wake ukapona."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWINGINE"," userResponse":" MWINGINE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671790220","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671790219"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru alijisikia ameondolewa na mzigo na mkia wake ukapona."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671790403","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671790403"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru alijisikia ameondolewa na mzigo na mkia wake ukapona."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671790944","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671790944"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru alijisikia ameondolewa na mzigo na mkia wake ukapona."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TATU"," userResponse":" TATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671793521","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671793520"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru alijisikia ameondolewa na mzigo na mkia wake ukapona."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" KUNGURU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671794901","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671794900"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru alijisikia ameondolewa na mzigo na mkia wake ukapona."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIJISIKIA"," userResponse":" ALIJISIKIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671796008","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671796007"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru alijisikia ameondolewa na mzigo na mkia wake ukapona."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMEONDOLEWA"," userResponse":" AMEONDOLEWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671796718","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671796717"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru alijisikia ameondolewa na mzigo na mkia wake ukapona."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671797501","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671797500"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru alijisikia ameondolewa na mzigo na mkia wake ukapona."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MZIGO"," userResponse":" MZIGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671797729","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671797728"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru alijisikia ameondolewa na mzigo na mkia wake ukapona."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671798354","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671798354"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru alijisikia ameondolewa na mzigo na mkia wake ukapona."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKIA"," userResponse":" MKIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671798851","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671798850"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru alijisikia ameondolewa na mzigo na mkia wake ukapona."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671799726","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671799724"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kunguru alijisikia ameondolewa na mzigo na mkia wake ukapona."," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UKAPONA"," userResponse":" UKAPONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671802469","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671802468"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Manyoya ya kunguru jinyonyoe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIIMBA"," userResponse":" ALIIMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671804238","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671804238"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Manyoya ya kunguru jinyonyoe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYOYA"," userResponse":" MANYOYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671804304","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671804304"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Manyoya ya kunguru jinyonyoe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671805402","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671805401"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Manyoya ya kunguru jinyonyoe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" KUNGURU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671806857","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671806857"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Manyoya ya kunguru jinyonyoe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JINYONYOE"," userResponse":" JINYONYOE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671809370","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671809370"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Manyoya ya kunguru jinyonyoe."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYOYA"," userResponse":" MANYOYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671809823","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671809823"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Manyoya ya kunguru jinyonyoe."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671810878","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671810878"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Manyoya ya kunguru jinyonyoe."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" KUNGURU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671812076","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671812075"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Manyoya ya kunguru jinyonyoe."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JINYONYOE"," userResponse":" JINYONYOE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671815035","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671815034"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Manyoya ya kunguru shikane yasijinyonyoe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" KATIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671816287","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671816287"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Manyoya ya kunguru shikane yasijinyonyoe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUITIKIA"," userResponse":" KUITIKIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671817151","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671817151"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Manyoya ya kunguru shikane yasijinyonyoe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FISI"," userResponse":" FISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671817998","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671817997"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Manyoya ya kunguru shikane yasijinyonyoe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIIMBA"," userResponse":" ALIIMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671818929","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671818928"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Manyoya ya kunguru shikane yasijinyonyoe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KINYUME"," userResponse":" KINYUME"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671820510","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671820509"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Manyoya ya kunguru shikane yasijinyonyoe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYOYA"," userResponse":" MANYOYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671820649","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671820649"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Manyoya ya kunguru shikane yasijinyonyoe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671821630","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671821629"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Manyoya ya kunguru shikane yasijinyonyoe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" KUNGURU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671822746","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671822746"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Manyoya ya kunguru shikane yasijinyonyoe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHIKANE"," userResponse":" SHIKANE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671824982","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671824981"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Manyoya ya kunguru shikane yasijinyonyoe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YASIJINYONYOE"," userResponse":" YASIJINYONYOE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671827903","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671827903"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Manyoya ya kunguru shikane yasijinyonyoe."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MANYOYA"," userResponse":" MANYOYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671828030","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671828030"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Manyoya ya kunguru shikane yasijinyonyoe."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671828990","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671828990"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Manyoya ya kunguru shikane yasijinyonyoe."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUNGURU"," userResponse":" KUNGURU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671830183","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671830182"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Manyoya ya kunguru shikane yasijinyonyoe."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHIKANE"," userResponse":" SHIKANE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671832054","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671832054"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Manyoya ya kunguru shikane yasijinyonyoe."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YASIJINYONYOE"," userResponse":" YASIJINYONYOE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671862757","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671862756"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Manyoya ya kunguru shikane yasijinyonyoe."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671862816","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671862816"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 4ad78fc1-5282-4edd-b73c-56e4f773d1b9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_67"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Manyoya ya kunguru shikane yasijinyonyoe."," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YASIJINYONYOE"," userResponse":" YASIJINYONYOE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:R..R.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.111","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671873619","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671873619"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 8a277cd7-8330-4f09-a3aa-4e2c77267372"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_R..R.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.111"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_r_b-r-j"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" r"," userResponse":" j"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:R..R.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.111","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671878882","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671878882"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 8a277cd7-8330-4f09-a3aa-4e2c77267372"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_R..R.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.111"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_r_b-r-j"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" r"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:R..R.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.111","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671884694","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671884693"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 8a277cd7-8330-4f09-a3aa-4e2c77267372"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_R..R.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.111"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_r_b-r-j"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" r"," userResponse":" r"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:R..R.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.111","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671889238","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671889238"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 8a277cd7-8330-4f09-a3aa-4e2c77267372"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_R..R.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.111"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_r_r-s-i"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" r"," userResponse":" r"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:R..R.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.111","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671892626","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671892625"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 8a277cd7-8330-4f09-a3aa-4e2c77267372"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_R..R.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.111"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_r_r-s-v"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" r"," userResponse":" r"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:R..R.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.111","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671896038","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671896037"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 8a277cd7-8330-4f09-a3aa-4e2c77267372"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_R..R.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.111"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_r_r-w-f"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" r"," userResponse":" r"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:R..R.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.111","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671900718","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671900718"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 8a277cd7-8330-4f09-a3aa-4e2c77267372"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_R..R.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.111"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_r_y-ch-r"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" r"," userResponse":" r"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:R..R.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.111","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671906094","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671906094"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 8a277cd7-8330-4f09-a3aa-4e2c77267372"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_R..R.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.111"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_r_l-r-o"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" r"," userResponse":" r"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:R..R.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.111","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671911136","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671911135"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 8a277cd7-8330-4f09-a3aa-4e2c77267372"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_R..R.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.111"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_r_t-r-y"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" r"," userResponse":" r"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:R..R.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.111","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671918389","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671918389"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 8a277cd7-8330-4f09-a3aa-4e2c77267372"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_R..R.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.111"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_r_p-r-g"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" r"," userResponse":" r"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:R..R.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.111","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671923577","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671923577"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 8a277cd7-8330-4f09-a3aa-4e2c77267372"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_R..R.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.111"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_r_r-i-w"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" r"," userResponse":" r"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:R..R.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.111","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671928971","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671928971"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 8a277cd7-8330-4f09-a3aa-4e2c77267372"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_R..R.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.111"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_r_m-r-n"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" r"," userResponse":" r"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:R..R.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.111","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548671934729","data":{"timestamp":" 1548671934728"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190128_132929"," gameId":" 8a277cd7-8330-4f09-a3aa-4e2c77267372"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_R..R.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.111"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_r_m-r-n"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}